haihoi.com 2009-12-07

# Links can post here

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to Haihoi.com. We value your privacy, and want you to know what information we collect and what we do with it. 

From time to time, we may make changes to this Policy. We will endeavor to   
post the changes before they become effective. The effective date of the most recent version of the privacy policy will appear at the top of this page. This consumer privacy policy applies to any information we collect or receive about you, from any source.

Haihoi.com takes your privacy seriously. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the websites provided by Haihoi.com

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
we have several areas where members can submit information to us, and we also have features that automatically collect information from our members and other users.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
We have certain areas where we ask you to provide information to us:

Registration: Haihoi.com, we will request some personal information, including your first and last name, your cell phone number, gender, age, and country to create your account. For the purpose for providing the Haihoi.com services, we may need you to provide your email address and password. We use your registration information to manage your account and to provide you with the Haihoi.com Services. Therefore, when you register as a member of Haihoi.com, you represent that you are providing complete and accurate information.

Communications from Us and Mailing Lists. In order to keep our members informed about the operation of our services, we will send e-mails and announcements that are needed for the proper functioning and administration of our site and subscription service. For additional information about our site, services and offers, we give our members the option of joining our mailing list. We also allow you to choose whether to receive mailings from partners and sponsors that we think will be of interest to you. You can always change your options in the "My Haihoi" section of the site under the "Edit Profile" subsection. Each marketing e-mail from us will come with instructions for how to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

Interactive Features. We also may offer interactive features, such as message boards, chat rooms, etc. Note that all personal information you send or post via such features becomes public information, and we are not responsible for any information you choose to make public (including any online identifier, such as an email address, instant messenger name or member name). We may store such information in an aggregate form but we will not file or retain such information on a personal basis. We may monitor such traffic via electronic software or personnel but only to check for obscenity, defamation or other types of abusive language, which we reserve the right to remove at any time.

Songs **.** The Audio files links on this page are only for evaluation use. If you decide to download any music file or any file for evaluation, you should delete them after 24 hours. If you don't, you will have to accept any consequences. All songs links provided in this page are for trial use only. Downloading at your own risk!!! 

Making cd from wmv-files, mp3-files and Video files is a violation of copyrights. The wmv-files, mp3-files and video files on this site are for evaluation use only. This website, its webmasters or its ISP cannot be held responsible for any consequences.

**COOKIES**

In order to provide you with personalized service, Haihoi.com uses "cookies" to keep and occasionally track information. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. The cookies that are gathered by Haihoi.com are only used by Haihoi.com at NO time do we share information from cookies with third parties.

We use these cookies to identify you as a valid subscriber so that we can deliver music to you, to ensure that no one else can sign on simultaneously with your account from another computer and to help us personalize your service experience based on your registration preferences (such as genre). We may also use session cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we provide. As part of the sign-in process, we may also use what are commonly called "persistent" cookies which stay with you after your session is over and you are offline. We only use these cookies in connection with a sign-in feature that allows you to save your member name and password so that the next time you sign in, these fields will be prepopulated for you.

For our internal purposes, we gather information such as date, time, connection speed and IP address of all visitors to our site. We keep this information simply for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, and system administration.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
Please note that, while using Haihoi.com, you could be directed to another site which is developed by people over whom Haihoi.com exercises no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.   
When you link to another site, you should review their privacy policy, as it may be different from our Privacy Policy. Haihoi.com is not responsible, and shall not be liable, for the privacy practices of linked sites or any use such sites may make of any information collected from you. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Site.

**LINKS**

We may display links to other sites within Haihoi.com. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

**INFORMATION SHARING**  
Haihoi.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

1\. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 

2\. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Haihoi 's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

3\. We transfer information about you if Haihoi.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Haihoi.com will notify you before information about you are transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

4\. We may use the information to communicate with you about our Services and to notify you of other Haihoi.com services that may be of interest.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**  
Haihoi.com exercises reasonable efforts to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that such information will be protected from actions outside of our control, such as computer hacking and physical theft. You acknowledge that you provide your personal information at your own risk.

**CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**   
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time.

**CONTACT US:**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the privacy practices of Haihoi.com, you can contact:
